{
  "questions": {
    "nominativ": [
      {
        "question": "Nominativ Maskulin",
        "answer": "der"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nominativ Faminin",
        "answer": "die"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nominativ Neutral",
        "answer": "das"
      },
      {
        "question": "Nominativ Plural",
        "answer": "die"
      }
    ],
    "genitiv": [
      {
        "question": "Genitiv Maskulin",
        "answer": "des"
      },
      {
        "question": "Genitiv Faminin",
        "answer": "der"
      },
      {
        "question": "Genitiv Neutral",
        "answer": "des"
      },
      {
        "question": "Genitiv Plural",
        "answer": "der"
      }
    ],
    "dativ": [
      {
        "question": "Dativ Maskulin",
        "answer": "dem"
      },
      {
        "question": "Dativ Faminin",
        "answer": "der"
      },
      {
        "question": "Dativ Neutral",
        "answer": "dem"
      },
      {
        "question": "Dativ Plural",
        "answer": "den"
      }
    ],
    "akkusativ": [
      {
        "question": "Akkusativ Maskulin",
        "answer": "den"
      },
      {
        "question": "Akkusativ Faminin",
        "answer": "die"
      },
      {
        "question": "Akkusativ Neutral",
        "answer": "das"
      },
      {
        "question": "Akkusativ Plural",
        "answer": "die"
      }
    ]
  },

  "articles": {
    "nominativ": ["der", "die", "das", "die"],
    "genitiv": ["des", "der", "des", "der"],
    "dativ": ["dem", "der", "dem", "den"],
    "akkusativ": ["den", "die", "das", "die"]
  }
}
